(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
本日はホロライブファンタジーファーストライブ
Thank you very much for coming to the Hololive Fantasy 1st Live
ファンファンアイランドにご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
FAN FUN ISLAND today.
公演を最後まで楽しんでいただくために、
To ensure everyone enjoys the performance until the very end,
皆様へいくつかご案内をさせてください。
please allow us to provide some instructions.
まずはじめに、会場の皆様へご案内です。
First, some instructions for those at the venue.
ロビー・客席内ではマスク着用が必須となります。
Masks must be worn at all times in the lobby and seating areas.
公演中の掛け声などは、
Please refrain from shouting or cheering during the performance
新型コロナウイルス感染予防の観点から、ご遠慮ください。
to help prevent the spread of COVID-19.
ぜひ、拍手やペンライトなどでの応援をお願いします。
Please show your support through applause and penlights instead.
ペンライトは、周りのお客様のご迷惑にならないよう、ご配慮をお願いします。
Please be mindful of other guests when using your penlights.
頭の上に出したり、大きく左右に振り回すと、
Raising them above your head or swinging them wildly
後ろのお客様や、周りのお客様のご迷惑となる場合がございます。
may disturb those behind or around you.
スタッフが注意させていただく場合がございますので、ご了承ください。
Please be aware that staff may step in if necessary.
また会場内では、立って応援いただいても問題ありませんが、
You are welcome to stand during the performance,
周りのお客様のご迷惑にならないよう、ご配慮をお願いいたします。
but please be considerate of those around you.
会場内では、スタッフの指示に従ってください。
Please follow the instructions of the staff within the venue.
周りのお客様に、ご迷惑をかけるような危険行為はご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from any dangerous behavior that may disturb other guests.
会場内では、携帯電話・スマートフォンはマナーモードに設定をお願いします。
Please set your mobile phones and smartphones to silent mode while inside the venue.
公演中、ライブの様子を撮影することは、演出の都合上、禁止といたします。
For production reasons, photography and recording of the live performance are prohibited.
以上のことが守られない場合、安全確保のため、
Failure to follow these rules may result in
公演を一時中断、もしくは中止させていただくこともございます。
the performance being paused or cancelled for safety reasons.
ご気分のすぐれない場合など、何かございましたら、
If you feel unwell or have any issues,
お早めに、お近くのスタッフにお申し付けください。
please inform a nearby staff member immediately.
また、地震などの緊急時には、スタッフが誘導いたします。
In the event of an emergency such as an earthquake, staff will guide you.
スタッフの指示があるまで、お席にてお待ちください。
Please remain in your seat until instructed.
また本公演は、映像配信及び、写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入るため、
Cameras for streaming and photography will be present,
お客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
and audience members may be captured in the footage.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーションや今後の活動に
These videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes
使用する可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
or future activities. Thank you for your understanding.
続いて、配信でご覧の皆様への注意事項をお伝えします。
Next, we have some notices for those watching via the live stream.
最善の準備を行い、ライブ配信を実施いたしますが、
We have taken every precaution for the stream,
生配信の特性上、不慮の障害で映像の乱れや
but due to its nature, technical issues or
一時停止などが起こる可能性があります。あらかじめご了承ください。
pauses may occur. Thank you for your understanding.
本ライブの録音・録画・ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りいたします。
Recording, filming, mirror streaming, or illegal uploads are strictly prohibited.
その代わり、スクリーンショットを撮影して画像とともにSNSに投稿していただくことは、大歓迎です！
Instead, we welcome you to take screenshots and post them on social media!
本公演のハッシュタグは、
The hashtag for today's performance is
ハッシュタグ「ホロライブ三期生ファーストライブ」です。
#ホロライブ3期生1stライブ.
ぜひハッシュタグを使って、ライブを一緒に盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag to help us get excited for the live show together!
それでは、開演まで今しばらくお待ちください。
Now, please wait a little longer until the show begins.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the show starts.
本日は、ホロライブファンタジー1stライブ FAN FUN ISLANDにご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for coming to Hololive Fantasy 1st Live FAN FUN ISLAND today.
大変長らくお待たせいたしました。本公演はまもなく開演いたします。
Thank you for waiting for so long. This performance will begin shortly.
会場の皆さんも、配信でご覧の皆さんも、一緒に盛り上がる準備はできてますかー？
Is everyone at the venue and everyone watching the stream ready to get hyped together?
それでは、いよいよ開演いたします。
Now, the show is finally about to begin.
ホロライブファンタジー1stライブ FAN FUN ISLAND、スタート！
Hololive Fantasy 1st Live FAN FUN ISLAND, start!
HOLOLIVE FANTASY 1st LIVE
FAN FUN ISLAND
3期生様 控室
HOLOLIVE FANTASY 1st LIVE
FAN FUN ISLAND
3rd Generation Members Dressing Room
よし じゃあ みんな集まったから 準備するか！
Alright, everyone's here, let's get ready!
ねぇ もうちょっと ゆっくり話そうぺこーだよー
Hey, let's talk a bit more, peko.
せっかくのライブだよ こうしてさ 久しぶりに5人で集まったわけだしさ
It's our special live concert. We finally gathered as five after a long time.
いやいやいや ライブだからこそ 準備しなきゃじゃん
No, no, no. Because it's a live, we have to prepare.
そな言うけどさ ぺこら なんか話したいことあんの？
You say that, but Pekora, is there something you want to talk about?
あるに決まってるぺこだよー
Of course there is, peko!
皆さん！ 好きな飲み物なに？
Everyone! What's your favorite drink?
えー？ そんなことー？ 今ライブの前に話すことじゃないだろ！
Eh? That's it? That's not something to talk about right before a live!
のーでもよくないぺこし 飲み物大事ぺこじゃねーの？
It doesn't matter, peko. Isn't drinking important, peko?
まぁ確かにね
Well, that's true.
某アールグレイティー
A certain Earl Grey tea.
出た 出た 出た！
There it is! There it is!
私も今日それー
I'm having that today too.
そんな感じで ちょっとるしあから今ブームして うちら全員これ飲んでるからな
Speaking of which, it's a trend started by Rushia, so we're all drinking this now.
だけどぺこらは飲んでないんだよねー
But Pekora isn't drinking it, right?
牛乳を飲んでるんだもんね ずっとずっと
You're drinking milk, aren't you? All the time.
牛乳うめーぺこじゃねーかよ！
Milk is delicious, peko!
美味しいけどね
It is tasty, though.
そういえば今日って そもそも何するんだっけ？
By the way, what are we even doing today?
ぺこら泣いてるんだけど
Pekora is crying.
泣かないで！ 何するんだっけ？ 何するんだっけ？
Don't cry! What were we doing again?
泣いてるぺこらをちょっとおいめに... 確かパーティーゲームじゃなかった？
Leaving the crying Pekora aside... wasn't it a party game?
そうそうそう 会場のみんなも参加できるゲームをね 用意しましたから
Right, right. I've prepared a game that everyone in the venue can join.
せっかくのライブだからね 歌ったりとかね わいわいやりたいじゃないですか
Since it's a live, we want to sing and have a blast, right?
いいじゃん 楽しそう
Sounds good. Seems fun.
ねー でもなんかドキドキたろうなんだけど 大丈夫？
Yeah, but I'm feeling a bit nervous. Is it okay?
え じゃあ ちゃんとさ ちょっとリハーサルとかしとかん？
Shouldn't we do a proper rehearsal or something?
でも結局さ やり始めてみないと分からないからさ
But in the end, we won't know until we start doing it.
とりあえずさ なんか 食べながら話さない？
For now, why don't we talk while eating?
どんだけぺこらやる気ないの
Pekora, how much motivation do you lack?
確かにね ライブ前なのに
True, even though it's before the live.
もう しょうがないな
Oh well, can't be helped.
まーでも これが私たちらしいって言えば 私たちらしいかな
Well, but if you say this is like us, then it's like us.
確かにね
True.
よっしゃ！ オッケー！ じゃあ景気づけに もう早速船長たち 3期生のライブを祝して 乾杯でもするか！
Alright! Okay! Then to kick things off, let's have a toast to celebrate our 3rd Gen live!
おー！
Yeah!
ちょっと待て待て待て ノエルお前何食べてんだお前！
Wait, wait, wait. Noel, what are you eating?!
え？ 何も食べてないわよ
Eh? I'm not eating anything.
食べてんじゃん！ 乾杯前に食べるな 何見てんだよ
You are eating! Don't eat before the toast! What are you looking at?
よし 食べよう 乾杯... るしあもなんか食べてる！
Alright, let's eat. Cheers... Rushia is eating something too!
コンビニのあのお肉が美味しいのでちゅ～
That meat from the convenience store is so delicious~
お肉は後ででしょ！ 先に食べるな
Meat is for later! Don't eat first!
ん？ あれ？ 誰？
Hmm? What? Who?
あれ？ なんか今
Wait, something just...
誰の声？ 今
Whose voice was that just now?
なんか聞こえたぺこ
I heard something, peko.
え 待って待って 声なんて聞こえた？
Eh, wait, wait. You heard a voice?
した した した！ ぺこらも聞こえたって
We did, we did! Pekora said she heard it too.
というかさ このボードゲームの水晶 光ってない？
Anyway, isn't the crystal on this board game glowing?
あ これね これ船長がね これ買ってきたんだわ
Ah, this? I bought this.
え？ あ 光ってるわ 光ってる
Eh? Ah, it is glowing. It's glowing.
光ってるよね？
It's glowing, right?
ちょっと待って なんか引っ張られとる！
Wait a minute, I'm being pulled in!
やばい やばい！ みんな 捕まって！
Oh no, oh no! Everyone, hang on!
見つけた... ようやく... 彼女たちが。
I found them... finally... those girls.
いんたらくとふぁんたじあ
Interact Fantasia
そわそわそわ 止まらないね
Restless, restless, it won't stop
いんたらくとふぁんたじあ
Interact Fantasia
いんたらくとふぁんたじあ きっとここは消えない
Interact Fantasia, this place surely won't disappear
めあふぁんたじあ いっそ
Mare Fantasia, might as well
だんだん目指すは頂点だ ほらついてくるぺこ
Gradually aiming for the top, come on, follow me, peko
ちょっちょっちょっと待って みんな一緒に ねぇねぇお頼り不甲斐ない
Wait, wait, wait, everyone together, hey, hey, your support is weak
怖いものなし 進めいざファイト
Fearless, move forward, now fight
たまには泣いたって 踏ん張って
Sometimes it's okay to cry, but hang in there
赤い手を取ってやってよ
Take this red hand
冒険の幕が開ける
The curtain rises on the adventure
まちまちすぎて良く機能
Too varied to function well
その目に焼き付け
Burn it into your eyes
広がる空も 海も大地も
The expanding sky, the sea, and the earth
重ね合った 想い出を溢れさせ
Let the overlapping memories overflow
明日へと 走り続けよう
Let's keep running toward tomorrow
果てしない 夢を追う まっすぐに
Chasing an endless dream, straight ahead
君となら 怖くないから
With you, I'm not afraid
戸惑いも全部
All the hesitation too
その背中に 預け合い
Entrusting it to each other's backs
道なき道も
Even pathless roads
楽しみながら 走れる
We can run while enjoying ourselves
心が今を告げる
The heart announces the present
さあ行こう
Let's go
進むべき未来が 待ってる
The future we should head toward is waiting
ほかでもない 君がいるから
Because you are there, no one else
つなげよう 君と僕の世界
Let's connect your world and mine
ここから 旅が始まってる
From here, the journey is starting
いんたらくとふぁんたじあ きっとここは消えない
Interact Fantasia, this place surely won't disappear
めあふぁんたじあ いっそ
Mare Fantasia, might as well
前触れ ハロー エブリデイ
Omen, hello everyday
日常を照らし出す クイックエコー
Lighting up daily life, quick echo
びっくり バイバイ 声上げた
Surprise, bye-bye, I cried out
ついて来れるよね？ ピー・カー・リー
You can follow, right? P-K-R
いま駆け出す 時は来た
The time to run out has come
心の準備は オッケー
Heart's preparation is okay
鐘を鳴らせば 伝説が
If the bell rings, the legend...
一歩開く
Opens a step
わずかに 踏み出した 勇気が
A little bit of courage stepped forward
になるから
...will become.
世界の果ても
Even to the end of the world,
次元の壁も
Even the walls of dimensions,
吹き飛ばして
Blow them all away,
今君に会いに行こう
Let's go see you now!
一緒に飛び出してみない？
Won't you jump out with us?
届かない夢はない どこででも
There's no dream that can't be reached, anywhere.
君とならたどり着けるから
Because with you, we can reach it.
奏でたいエールを
The cheers we want to play,
その両手に握りしめ
Clasp them in both your hands.
真っ白の地図を
A blank map,
描き回して駆け出そう
Draw it out and start running.
願い事共に歌う
Singing together with our wishes,
聞こえるよ 目映いしのファンタジー明けても
I can hear it, even after the dazzling fantasy dawns.
出会いは幻じゃないから
Because our meeting is not an illusion.
つなげよう君と僕の奇跡を
Let's connect your miracle and mine.
奏で合うシンフォニー
A symphony playing together.
いつまでも
Forever...
ちょっと強くなりたくて
Wanting to become a little stronger,
ずっと笑い合いたくて
Wanting to keep laughing together,
色づく気持ち一歩進んで君と出会えたよ
Stepping forward with coloring feelings, I met you.
失敗も公開もさせるわけないよ
I won't let there be failure or regret.
だって毎日楽しすぎるでしょ
Because every day is just too much fun.
時折の先の先へ
Beyond the beyond of sometimes.
裸足で駆けるけど
Running barefoot, but...
ここは？
Where am I?
海？
The ocean?
ていうか、え、ここどこ？
Wait, where is this?
あ、気がついた？
Oh, you're awake?
うわっ、さっきの声！
Whoa, that voice from before!
おー、ようやく起きたか。
Oh, you're finally awake.
まった、おせーぺこ！
Geez, you're slow peko!
ノエル、ペコラ...
Noel, Pekora...
その隣にいるのって...
The one next to you...
あ、どうも、妖精です。
Ah, hello. I'm a fairy.
は？
Huh?
いや、だから妖精です。この島の。名前はミズカって言います。
I said, I'm a fairy. Of this island. My name is Mizuka.
え？どういうこと？
Eh? What do you mean?
ミズカさん、は、初めまして。
M-Mizuka-san, nice to meet you.
いやいや、ていうか妖精って！それにどうやってここに？
Wait, a fairy?! And how did we get here?
まあ驚くのも無理ないぺこ。ぺこらたちも少し前に起きたんだけど、同じような反応だったからね。
Well, it's no wonder you're surprised peko. We woke up a little while ago too, and had the same reaction.
あん、で。驚かないで聞いてほしいんじゃけど...
Now then. I want you to listen without getting surprised...
なんと、ここは異世界の無人島なんじゃ！
Incredibly, this is a deserted island in another world!
えーー！？どういうこと！？
Whaaat?! What do you mean?!
いや、今流行りの異世界転生っていうんかな。現実とは違う世界に来ちゃったみたいなんよね。
Well, I guess it's what they call "Isekai Reincarnation" that's popular now. It seems we've come to a world different from reality.
そんなファンタジーなことってある？
Can such a fantasy thing actually happen?
って、まあ私たちが言うのも変なんだけどさ。
Though, I guess it's weird for us to be saying that.
たしかに。
True.
ホロライブファンタジーやし。
We are Hololive Fantasy, after all.
えー、ていうことはさっきの水晶に引きずり込まれちゃったってことかな？
Eh, so does that mean we were dragged into that crystal from earlier?
そうそう。
Exactly.
それでね、なんかミズカさんからお願いがあって。
And you see, Mizuka-san has a request for us...
それよりも！
More importantly!
お？
Oh?
重要なことに気がつかないぺこか？
Don't you notice something important peko?
え？重要なこと？
Eh? Something important?
妖精、海、と言ったらこれっきゃない！
Fairy, ocean... there's only one thing!
ノエちゃん、歌うぺこ！
Noe-chan, sing peko!
いやいや、いきなり！？
Wait, all of a sudden!?
妖精たちと胸を刺激する
With the fairies, stimulating our hearts,
生足魅惑のマーメイド
A mermaid with charming bare legs.
出すとこ出してたわわになったら
Showing what's there, when they become ripe,
本物の恋はやれ爽快
Real love is so refreshing.
ほんまの恋が できそうかい
Think you can fall in love for real?
ごまかしきかない薄着の曲線は
確信犯のしなやかなスタイル
The curves of thin clothes that can't be hidden
A supple style with criminal intent
耐水性のトキメキ 変わる瞬間のまぶしさは
いかがなもの
Water-resistant heartbeats, how about the
brightness of the moment things change?
心まで脱がされる熱い風の誘惑に
To the temptation of the hot wind
that strips even the heart
乗っちゃってかまわないから
真夏は不祥事も君次第で
It's okay to get on board, because
midsummer scandals are up to you
YO SAY 夏を刺激する 生足魅惑のマーメイド
YO SAY, stimulating summer,
a mermaid with enchanting bare legs
出すとこ出して たわわになったら
宝物の恋ができそうかい
Show what you've got, and when you're ripe
think you can fall in love with a treasure?
Ｔシャツじゃなくても ボディガードにもなるよ
熱いパナマの 帽子ゆずって
Even without a T-shirt, I'll be your bodyguard
Let me have your hot Panama hat
隙を見せたら不意に耳に入る
サービスギャグなんかで涼みたくない
If you show a gap, it suddenly enters your ears
I don't want to cool down with service gags
むせ返る熱帯夜を彩る花火のように
Like fireworks coloring
the suffocating tropical night
打ち上げて散る想いなら
このまま抱き合って焦がれるまで
If it's thoughts that launch and scatter
then let's keep hugging until we burn
YO SAY 夏を刺激する 熱い欲望はトルネイド
YO SAY, stimulating summer,
hot desires are a tornado
出すもの出して 素直になりたい
君と僕とならオール・オーライ
Put it all out, I want to be honest
If it's you and me, it's all right
都会のビルの海じゃ感じなくなってる君を
You, who have stopped feeling
in the sea of city buildings
誘い込んでの口づけで
酔わせてとろかして差し上げましょう
With an inviting kiss
I'll make you drunk and melt you
YO SAY 夏を刺激する 生足ヘソ出しマーメイド
YO SAY, stimulating summer,
a bare-legged, belly-baring mermaid
恋にかまけて お留守になるのも
脳天気的にもオール・オーケー
Neglecting things for love
it's all okay, even for the carefree
YO SAY 夏を誰としたくなる
独り寝の夜にユー・キャン・セイ・グッバイ
YO SAY, you'll want to spend summer with someone
Say goodbye to sleeping alone
奥の方まで 乾く暇ないほど
ほんまの恋をしませんか
Deep down, until there's no time to dry
won't you fall in love for real?
HOLOLIVE FANTASY 1st LIVE
FAN FUN ISLAND
イエーイ！
Yay!
どーもぺこー。よかったんだけど、そうじゃなくて。
もっと突っ込むとこあるじゃん。
Hello-peko. It was good, but that's not it.
There's more to call out, right?
いやいやふーたん。今船長めっちゃあったまったからね。
しかもね、かすかにお客さんの手拍子まで伝わってきた気がする。
No, no, Fuutan. I'm really fired up now.
Plus, I think I could even faintly hear the audience clapping.
いや、確かに歌ってたら、ライブ会場のような
不思議な感覚がしたぺこ。
Yeah, it's true, while singing, it felt strangely
like a live venue-peko.
そしたら、船長の歌しかないでしょ！
Then, it's gotta be Captain's song!
いやいやもう君たち！いるなら手拍子やコメントで
合いの手入れて、存在をアピールしてください！
Hey, you guys! If you're there, please show your presence
with claps and comments!
あほーい！我ら宝鐘海賊団、出航ー！
Ahoy! We are the Houshou Pirates, setting sail!
出航ー！にょそろー！
Setting sail! Nyosora!
海賊ならヨーホー 踊れ叫べヨーホー
さあ今 旗の下へ
If you're a pirate, Yo-ho! Dance and shout, Yo-ho!
Now, come under the flag
宝鐘海賊団 出航ー！
Houshou Pirates, setting sail!
あほーい！ あほーい！ あほーい！
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
Ahoy!! 我ら宝鐘海賊団☆
Ahoy!! We are the Houshou Pirates☆
踊るあほーい 見るあほーい
Dancing fools, watching fools
全速前進だー！
Full speed ahead!
進め 進め 大洋はさんざん 大航海日和だ
Forward, forward, the ocean is brilliant
It's a great day for a voyage
歌え 歌え 太鼓のテンション 波の音に乗せて どんぶらこ
Sing, sing, with the tension of the drums
Riding the sound of the waves, donburako
海でまるく旅 おかげ 陽気がハッピー
A peaceful journey at sea, thanks to that
the mood is happy
お空ではドクロくん キラキラ
In the sky, Dokuro-kun is sparkling
山奥ボロボロマイハウスで 夢を見て
Dreaming in my run-down house deep in the mountains
あー、神様、いつかこのマリンを本物の海賊にしてください！
Ah, God, please make this Marine a real pirate someday!
声をあげて　さあ出航だ
Raise your voice, it's time to set sail
我ら宝鐘海賊団だ
We are the Houshou Pirates
コンパス片手に旗を掲げ
With compass in hand and flag raised
この海をジャックしちゃおう
Let's hijack this sea
余さず付いておいで
Follow along without exception
共にヨーホーヨーホー叫ぼう
Let's shout 'Yo-ho, yo-ho' together
あー、最高の今日に
Ah, to the best day ever
ようこそ我が船
Welcome to my ship
アホイ！アホイ！アホイ！アホイ！
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
踊るアホイに見るアホイ　アホイ！アホイ！アホイ！アホイ！
Dancing Ahoy, watching Ahoy. Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
アホイ！アホイ！ホイホイホイ！
Ahoy! Ahoy! Hoi hoi hoi!
1, 2, サンバ, サンバ！
1, 2, Samba, Samba!
熱く語ろうよパッション
Let's talk passionately
思いを解き放って
Release your thoughts
赤く煌めくパッション
Red sparkling passion
形から入るタイプです
I'm the type who starts with appearance
発射10秒前
10 seconds before launch
走れ合図入れたら
Run when the signal is given
無茶も通るわ　ギラギラ
Even the unreasonable will pass, glaring
じんわり汗も滴るいい女　だけど
A fine woman slowly dripping with sweat, but...
あー、神様、船長はセンシティブだとBANされちゃうのですね、はにゃー！
Ah, God, the Captain will get banned if she's sensitive, right? Hanyah!
奪われたら　取り戻せ
If it's stolen, take it back
それが宝鐘海賊団だ
That's the Houshou Pirates
君たちとなら辿り着ける
With all of you, we can reach it
伝説のエルドラド
The legendary El Dorado
余さず楽しけりゃ
If we're enjoying it without exception
歌えヨーホーヨーホー　ハニー
Sing 'Yo-ho, yo-ho', honey
あー、この景色
Ah, this scenery
大切な仲間よ
Our precious comrades
宴だ宴だ　騒げや騒げ
It's a banquet! Make some noise!
踊るアホイに見るアホイ　アホイ！
Dancing Ahoy, watching Ahoy. Ahoy!
同じアホなら呑まなきゃ損々
Since we're all fools, it's a loss not to drink
宝刀片手に行き過ぎよーそれ
Going too far with a treasured sword in hand
アホイ！アホイ！アホイ！アホイ！
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
宝鐘マリン！
Houshou Marine!
世界で一番、アホイーヨー！
The biggest Ahoy in the world!
滅殺！滅殺！滅殺！滅殺！
Destroy! Destroy! Destroy! Destroy!
エロがき！エロがき！エロがき！エロがき！
Ero-brat! Ero-brat! Ero-brat! Ero-brat!
ボンキュッボン！
Voluptuous!
お嬢ちゃん、パンツ何色？
Hey girl, what color are your panties?
パンツは何色？
What color are your panties?
お宝！お宝！
Treasure! Treasure!
もぞい！もぞい！
Mozoi! Mozoi!
ノデもズドン！
Nodemusu-don!
船長のいいとこ見てみたい
I want to see the Captain's good side
見てみたい、見てみたい！
I want to see, I want to see!
アハハーン
A-ha-haan
もっともっと！
More, more!
ウフフーン
U-fu-fuun
もっともっと！
More, more!
セクシーに
Sexily
もっともっと！
More, more!
いっはいマイチン
Ihai Maichin
もっともっと！
More, more!
脱いじゃお
Let's take it off
もっともっと！
More, more!
サービスサービス
Service, service
もっともっと！
More, more!
萌え萌えキュン
Moe moe kyun
もっともっと！
More, more!
出会って5秒で
5 seconds after meeting
合唱だ！
It's a chorus!
あーもう！船長は君たちをそんな子に育てた覚えはありません！本当に！ねえ、だぞ！
Ah, enough! The Captain doesn't remember raising you to be like that! Seriously! Right, dazo!
立てば自嘲、座れば自嘲、歩く姿はセンシティブ
Standing is self-mockery, sitting is self-mockery, walking is sensitive
夢も見ようよ　この船で
Let's dream on this ship
後悔なんてさせない
I won't let you regret it
君たちのおかげで私は
Thanks to all of you, I
船長になれるから
Can become the Captain
ミラクル船長カノン　撃てー！
Miracle Captain Cannon, fire!
声をあげて　さあ出航だ
Raise your voice, it's time to set sail
我ら宝鐘海賊団だ
We are the Houshou Pirates
コンパス片手に旗を掲げ
With compass in hand and flag raised
この海をジャックしちゃおう
Let's hijack this sea
余さず付いておいで
Follow along without exception
共にヨーホーヨーホー叫ぼう
Let's shout 'Yo-ho, yo-ho' together
あー、最高の今日に
Ah, to the best day ever
ようこそ我が船
Welcome to my ship
宝鐘の海賊だー！
It's the Houshou pirate!
それではいきますよ！出航！
Here we go! Set sail!
いぇーい！すごかった！
Yay! That was amazing!
いやー、ちょっとやっぱ分かった。やっぱりこれね、
Yeah, I definitely figured it out. This is definitely...
リスナーさん間違いなくいるぞ。感じた。
The listeners are here for sure. I felt it.
みんなも歌ったほうがいい。
Everyone should sing too.
マジか？
Really?
なるほど。
I see.
とりあえずはみんなで一緒に歌って、状況整理しよってことかな？
So, basically, let's all sing together and sort out the situation?
うす！そんな狙いが。
Yes! That's the plan.
フレア、ノエル、一緒に歌おう！
Flare, Noel, let's sing together!
えっ、ちょっと待って、団長2回目なんだけど。
Wait, it's the second time for the Knight Commander.
いくよ！えー！
Here we go! Ei!
パッパッパッと晴れやかに
Brightly and vividly
咲かせましょう　花のよう
Let's make them bloom like flowers
...空へと
...to the sky.
弱気な心を開ける魔法のキー
A magic key that opens a timid heart.
それでもいい海 勢いよく跳ねて
Even so, jump vigorously into the sea.
始まる夢は...
The dream that begins...
夢はどんな形
What shape is the dream?
踊れや踊れ 散らさないで
Dance, dance, don't let it scatter.
もっともっと一緒に数えたい
I want to count more and more together
新しい景色
the new scenery.
いろはにホパッとパッと晴れやかに
Iroha ni, hop, and suddenly, it's bright.
咲かせましょう花のように
Let's make it bloom like a flower.
これからの君が見たい
I want to see the future you.
いろはにホパッとパッと晴れやかに
Iroha ni, hop, and suddenly, it's bright.
咲かせる思いは常ならむ
The feelings that bloom are not eternal.
だっておとめ道は風任せだと
Because the maiden's path is left to the wind,
呟いてみた
I tried whispering.
おとめごころさ
It's a maiden's heart.
迷ってるだけなら何も起こらない
If you just hesitate, nothing will happen.
強気で行くんだと瞳で語るよ
I'll tell you with my eyes to be strong.
そしたらさおいで 明日がぴかぴかと
Then come on, tomorrow will be sparkling
輝く夢の
shining dream...
夢の色に変わる
changing to the color of the dream.
歌えや歌え 浮かれながら
Sing, sing, while making merry.
ずっとずっと一緒に遊びたい
I want to play together forever and ever
サクラ色ハーモニー
in a cherry blossom colored harmony.
散りぬるをさっとさっと流れてく
Scattering quickly, quickly flowing away,
うたかたの花の香り
the fleeting scent of flowers.
いつまでも君といたい
I want to be with you forever.
散りぬるをさっとさっと流れてく
Scattering quickly, quickly flowing away,
出会いと別れに酔いもせず
without getting drunk on meetings and partings.
そっと見つめ合って
Gently looking at each other,
君の気配を感じていたい
I want to feel your presence.
おとめの願い
A maiden's wish.
踊れや今こんなに嬉しくて
Dance now, I'm so happy,
踊れほらこんなに嬉しくて
dance, see, I'm so happy,
気分次第で遠くへ飛べそう
I feel like I could fly far away depending on my mood.
歌えや今こんなに楽しくて
Sing now, I'm having so much fun,
歌えほらこんなに楽しくて
sing, see, I'm having so much fun,
ずっともっと一緒に遊びたい
I want to play together more and more forever,
気持ちが奏でる
my feelings playing
サクラ色ハーモニー
a cherry blossom colored harmony.
いろはにホパッとパッと晴れやかに
Iroha ni, hop, and suddenly, it's bright.
咲かせましょう花のように
Let's make it bloom like a flower.
これからの君が見たい
I want to see the future you.
いろはにホパッとパッと晴れやかに
Iroha ni, hop, and suddenly, it's bright.
咲かせる思いは常ならむ
The feelings that bloom are not eternal.
だっておとめ道は風任せだと
Because the maiden's path is left to the wind,
呟いてみた
I tried whispering.
おとめごころさ
It's a maiden's heart.
いろはにほへと
Irohanihoheto
知りたくないの
I don't want to know.
イエーイ！ アガるー！
Yay! This is exciting!
この歌、この気持ち、このお客さんみんなの反応... やっぱり僕は間違ってなかった。
This song, these feelings, the reaction from all these guests... I wasn't wrong after all.
えっ？ おっ？ どういうこと？
Eh? Oh? What do you mean?
ていうか確かに、歌うごとにお客さんの気配を感じるんだけど。
I mean, it's true, I feel the presence of the guests with every song.
ふふっ。この島は、音楽とそれを楽しむ気持ちこそが力の源になっているんだ。
Hehe. On this island, music and the feelings of enjoying it are the source of power.
おお〜！
Ooh~!
今までの歌を聴いて、そして見ているお客さんのワクワクする心を感じて確信したよ。この世界を救うために、君たちの、
Listening to the songs so far, and feeling the excitement in the hearts of the guests watching, I'm certain now. To save this world, I need your...
そしてこのライブを見ている皆さんの力を貸してください。
...and the strength of everyone watching this live. Please lend me your power.
え〜、いや〜もう助けてあげたい気持ちはもちろんあるんだけどさあ。
Well, I mean, of course I want to help you...
それだったらちょっとライブ会場でお客さんも待ってるし、例えば一度元の世界に返してもらってからとかでもいい？
But the guests are waiting at the live venue, so could you maybe send us back to our original world first or something?
それが、この世界にみんなを呼ぶのに最後の力を使っちゃって...
The thing is, I used the last of my power to bring everyone to this world...
ええー！？
Eeeeh!?
じゃあ、どうしたらいいのー？
Then, what should we do?
巻き込んじゃってごめんなさい。
I'm sorry for dragging you all into this.
でもこの島の様子はみんなにもこうやって伝わって...
But the state of this island is being conveyed to everyone like this...
し、この島の力を取り戻したら、みんなのことはちゃんと元の世界に戻せるから。
And once I've restored this island's power, I'll be able to return you all to your original world.
るしあちゃん、謝らないで。
Rushia-chan, please don't apologize.
まあ、そういうことならしょうがないでしょう。
Well, if that's the case, it can't be helped.
無人島探索、しかも異世界だからね。せっかくなら、
Desert island exploration, and in another world too. Since we're here...
楽しむしかないっしょ！
...we might as well enjoy it!
まあ確かに、ある意味夢のような経験ではあるしね！
Well, certainly, in a sense, it's a dream-like experience!
会場のみんなも配信で見てるみんなもいいぺこか？
Is it good for everyone in the venue and everyone watching the stream, peko?
ぺこらたちは今異世界にいるんだけど、みんなのことも見えてるよ！
Pekora and the others are in another world right now, but we can see all of you!
みんなが楽しむ気持ちも必要だから、ちゃんと盛り上がってぺこね！
We need your excitement too, so make sure to get hyped up, peko!
イエーイ！
Yay!
みんな、ありがとう。
Everyone, thank you.
うーん、でも具体的には何をすればいいんじゃろうか？
Hmm, but specifically, what should we do?
うん。まずはそのあたりを説明するね。
Yeah. First, I'll explain all that.
でも、いつまでも海辺だとあれだから、一旦森の方に移動しながらにしよう。
But we can't stay on the beach forever, so let's move toward the forest while we talk.
うん、そうしようか。
Yeah, let's do that.
森か。久しぶりだなあ。
The forest, huh? It's been a while.
あ、そっか。エルフ、エルフの森！
Oh, that's right. An elf, an elf's forest!
エルフの森ぺこか。エルフの森だったっけ？
An elf's forest, peko? Was it an elf's forest?
ご両親にご挨拶しなきゃ。
I have to greet your parents.
いないでしょ！無人島ぺこだって！
They're not there! I said it's a desert island, peko!
エルフの森だから。
Because it's an elf forest.
無料パートはここまでになるので、続きはよければチケットを買って楽しんでね！
The free part ends here, so please buy a ticket and enjoy the rest if you'd like!
みんなの力も必要になるから、ぜひよろしくお願いします。
We'll need everyone's help too, so please look forward to it.
ん？なんか言った？おー？
Hmm? Did you say something? Oh?
じゃあ、早速行こう！
Well, let's go!
おー！
Oh!
楽しみだね。めっちゃ楽しみだね。
I'm looking forward to it. Really looking forward to it.
HOLOLIVE FANTASY 1st LIVE FAN FUN ISLAND
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free part has ended
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!